Guide to the John Vance Lauderdale Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
The doctor reported to Fort Omaha, Nebraska in March 1895 after a long leave. Omaha was a growing city and his journals provide an excellent view of life there during the mid-1890s. He visited the city waterworks, rode the street cars, attended the state fair and a performance of Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show, and took the family to the city's "Coney island," a place called Manowah on the Iowa side of the Missouri River. Aside from a diphtheria epidemic in early 1896, his medical duties were not onerous. He noted that in July 1895 ninety-one soldiers needed treatment, most for bowel troubles brought on by eating too much green fruit. He also reported attending a "pyro-military spectacle" on the siege of Vicksburg and a lecture by General O. O. Howard on the Battle of Gettysburg.
The final section of Series I, Boxes 14-16, covers a twenty year retirement period. Before retirement on November 13, 1896, however, he spent a month's leave in Denver. The family remained there until the end of November and vacationed in Salt Lake City, San Francisco, Pacific Grove, Los Angeles, and San Diego for the next six months.
In August 1897 the Lauderdales moved into a new house on 84th Street in Brooklyn and a great deal of the remaining material consists of newspaper clippings, programs, invitations, and the like that document his social activities. The collection contains, for example, programs for a 1904 performance of "Sherlock Holmes" with William Gillette in the title role, the 1908 graduation exercises for the Polytechnic Preparatory School of Brooklyn, the 1909 reunion and dinner of The Society of Alumni of Bellevue Hospital, and for a 1910 performance of J. M. Barrie's "What Every Woman Knows" featuring Maude Adams. Scattered journal entries continue until 1903.
Significant groups of letters are only found in the years 1903, 1910, 1915, and 1916. Dr. Lauderdale described the final illness and death of sister Frank and poor health of brother Robert in Geneseo in letters to his wife written in July and August 1903. Additional letters written in August and September by Louise Lauderdale, Robert's wife, and brother Walter describe Robert's last days. In a small group of July 1910 letters, Lauderdale, again writing from Geneseo, discussed the health of brothers Walter and Willis, while in several 1915 letters to Willis the doctor talked about family news. The last group of letters date from June and July 1916 and describe a trip made by the doctor to Fort Grant in the Canal Zone to visit his daughter and her family.
As has been noted, the Lauderdale Papers contain scattered information on American politics, religion, alcoholism and temperance, gardening, family life and child rearing practices, and the fate of Indians in the western United States. The papers also include material documenting the doctor's interest in photography and science and his views of blacks, plus information on such subjects as the lives of servants, death, and dying.
Dr. Lauderdale had an abiding interest in photography. He collected photographs, was an ardent amateur photographer, and enjoyed showing his pictures. It is possible that some of the lantern slides stored in Boxes 17-18 were included in his many "lantern entertainments." The bulk of the photographs in his scrapbooks are of friends, acquaintances, and family, or of the places the doctor was stationed or visited. The collection contains photographic images of all of Lauderdale's major posts from Fort Yuma to Fort Omaha, plus an extensive series of photographs documenting the Lauderdale family's six-month vacation after the doctor's retirement in 1896.
Lauderdale was also an amateur artist, and about seventy drawings and sketches are found among the contents of his scrapbooks. The scrapbooks also include a drawing by a wounded soldier in October 1867, a drawing by an "Indian boy" in December 1872, and a three sketches by a "Dr. Macauley" in 1883 and 1884. Most of Lauderdale's own drawings are in the first three volumes of his scrapbook collection, with a few scattered in the volumes that document later periods of his life.
Lauderdale was interested in science in a general way, and in 1856 was elected a member of the American Association for the Advancement of Science. He collected fossils in the 1850s, read about telephone, phonograph, and electric light experiments in the late 1870s, viewed comets, undertook experiments with sulfate of iron in 1883, and gave lectures to military personnel on chemistry and anatomy. As early as April 1879, while stationed at Mount Vernon Barracks, Alabama, he set up a telephone to connect his quarters with the post hospital. His journals for the next several years contain numerous references to setting up and using telephones on army bases.
Lauderdale's journals also contain observations on black life and frequent references to blacks, such as the soldiers of the 9th Cavalry and his black cook, David Crockett Moore, who was part of the Lauderdale household for almost twenty-four years. The doctor sometimes expressed stereotypical sentiments; writing, for example, in April 1879 that the riverboat deckhands were never "too fatigued to sing," and in July 1888 that "colored people are very tender and will always stop work when there is a little something wrong with them." On the other hand, he believed in their right to vote, attended services at black churches in the South, and provided financial assistance to at least one poverty stricken black seeking to further her education. In June 1894 W. A. C. Caldwell of Mobile, Alabama wrote to thank him for his help in allowing her to get a first grade teaching certificate. Lauderdale sometimes noted the prejudice that blacks had to endure. In January 1876 he questioned the need to keep separate medical records for black soldiers, and in July 1882 he noted that the washerwomen at Fort Sully did not wish to wash David's clothes.
The illnesses and deaths of Lauderdale's mother in 1882, daughter in 1885, sister Nettie in 1888, father in 1893, sister Frank in 1903, and brother Robert that same year are all well documented, as are such topics as the life of an army wife, raising children on military posts, and the more general subject of family life in the army during the last third of the nineteenth century.
Series II, Family Papers, is housed in Box 16. The materials in this series consist of genealogical material, newspaper clippings, obituaries for Lauderdale and his wife, and a typescript copy of Lauderdale's 1922 will.
Series III. Lantern Slides, are housed in Boxes 17 and 18. Many of the glass plate lantern slides duplicate photographs found elsewhere in the collection. They have been arranged in chronological order to the extent possible; slides that could not be identified with a particular career location have been filed at the end. The collection holds ninety lantern slides, Most of the slides appear to be the work of Dr. Lauderdale, but some were commercially produced. Box 18, numbers 46-48, for example, contains three lantern slides of Utah sold by "W. H. Jackson & Co., Denver, Colo."
Box 19 houses Oversize material, most of which was removed from Lauderdale's scrapbooks. An 1838 land grant to Samuel Vance for property in Michigan is present, along with a number of printed programs, clippings, and other items.
Appendix: Guide to Microfilm
2 1-2 28-57 Ms Vault Film 2535
3 2-3 58-82 Ms Vault Film 2536
4 3 83-111 Ms Vault Film 2537
5 4 112-151 Ms Vault Film 2536
6 4-5 152-183 Ms Vault Film 2539
7 5-6 184-219 Ms Vault Film 2540
8 6 220-233 Ms Vault Film 2841
9 7-8 234-279 Ms Vault Film 2585
10 8-9 280-316 Ms Vault Film 2586
11 9-10 317-354 Ms Vault Film 2587
12 10 355-395 Ms Vault Film 2798
13 11 396-429 Ms Vault Film 2799
14 12 430-466 Ms Vault Film 2800
15 13-14 467-500 Ms Vault Film 2801
16 14-15 501-536 Ms Vault Film 2802
17 16 537-565 Ms Vault Film 2803
18 19 566-582 Ms Vault Film 2804
Fort Davis (Tex.); Fort Lowell (Ariz.); Fort Omaha (Neb.); Fort Ontario (N.Y.); Fort Sully (S.D.); Fort Wingate (N.M.); African Americans -- Social conditions; Alcoholism; Army spouses; Pullman Strike, 1894; Dakota Indians; Draft Riot, New York, N.Y., 1863; Families; Indians of North America -- Government relations; Indians of North America -- Missions; Indians of North America -- Arizona; Indians of North America -- New Mexico; Indians of North America -- South Dakota; Indians of North America -- Wyoming; Medicine, Military; Mormons -- Utah; Navajo Indians; Presbyterians -- United States; Women; Zuni Indians; Alabama -- Description and travel; Arizona -- Description and travel; Atlanta (Ga.) -- Description and travel; Fort Bridger (Wyo.); Fort Clark (Tex.); Fort Concho (Tex.); Geneseo (N.Y.) -- History; New Mexico -- History; New York (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs; Omaha (Neb.) -- Social life and customs; Oswego (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs; Pine Ridge Indian Reservation (S.D.); Presidio of San Francisco (Calif.); Saint Louis (Mo.) -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; San Francisco (Calif.) -- Description and travel; South Dakota -- History; Texas -- History -- 1846-1950; Tucson (Ariz.) -- Description and travel; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865 -- Medical care; Utah -- History; Yuma (Ariz.) -- Description and travel; Drawings -- United States; Lantern slides -- United States; Photographs -- United States; Photographers -- United States; Physicians -- United States; Soldiers -- United States; Lauderdale, John Vance, 1832-1931; Moore, David Crockett; Stewart, Antoinette Williams, d. 1884; United States. Army ( Military life); United States. Army ( Surgeons); Bellevue Hospital; Fort Bennett (S.D.); Fort Yuma (Ariz.); McPherson Barracks (Ga.); Mount Vernon Barracks (Ala.)
- Scrapbooks, 1850-1917; Series I; 6; (16 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, Scrapbooks, is organized into thirteen subseries, one for each scrapbook. Pages in these bound volumes were frequently layered with multiple items. Unpaginated photographs, sketches and printed ephemera were also interleaved. Material is arranged to approximate these complex physical relationships. Folder titles refer to the pagination of the bound volume, not the amount of material in folder. Dates are for the principal material. Volumes I-III are primarily correspondence. Volumes IV-X include journal entries. Volumes XI-XII are a mixture of correspondence, journal entries and printed materials. Volume XIII is predominantly printed material: invitations, programs, and other works.
  - VOLUME I, 1850-1862
    - Index (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - p. 1-5, 1850-52 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - p. 6-7, 1852 Jan (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - p. 8-13, 1852 Feb-Apr (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - p. 14-19, 1852 Apr-Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - p. 20-26, 1852 Jul (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - p. 27-32, 1852 Aug-Sep (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - p. 34-38, 1852 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - p. 39-44, 1853 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - p. 45-49, 1853 May-Sep (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - p. 50-55, 1853 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - p. 56-62, 1854 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - p. 63-68, 1854 Jun-Aug (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - p. 69-73, 1854 Sep-Dec (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - p. 74-76, 1855 Aug-Sep (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - p. 77-82, 1855 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - p. 83-86, 1855 Dec (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - p. 87-96, 1856 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - p. 97-106, 1856 May-Sep (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - p. 107-112, 1856 Oct-Nov (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - p. 113-121, 1857 Jan-Apr (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - p. 122-127, 1857 May (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - p. 129-137, 1857 Jul-Nov (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - p. 138-144, 1858 Jan-Oct (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - p. 145-154, 1858 Nov-Dec (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - p. 155-162, 1859 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - p. 163-168, 1859 Apr-Dec (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - p. 169-173, 1860 Jan-Feb (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - p. 174-177, 1860 May-Oct (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - p. 178-183, 1861 Jan-Aug (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - p. 184-190, 1861 Sep-Nov (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - p. 191-201, 1861 Dec (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - p. 202-208, 1862 Jan-Mar (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - p. 210-213, 1862 Mar (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - VOLUME II, 1862-1865
    - Index (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - p. 1-5, 1862 Apr (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - p. 6-15, 1862 Apr (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - p. 16-28, 1862 May (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - p. 29-32, 1862 Jun (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - p. 33-39, 1862 Jul (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - p. 40-44, 1862 Jul-Aug (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - p. 45-49, 1862 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - p. 50-55, 1862 Aug 18-28 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - p. 56-59, 1862 Oct (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - p. 60-62, 1862 Nov (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - p. 63-67, 1862 Dec (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - p. 68-71, 73-79, 1863 Jan-Feb (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - p. 80-88, 1863 Mar-Apr (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - p. 89-93, 1863 May (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - p. 94-97, 1863 Jun (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - p. 98-102, 1863 Jul (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - p. 103-105, 1863 Aug-Sep (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - p. 106-109, 1863 Oct (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - p. 110-119, 1863 Nov-Dec (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - p. 121-126, 1864 Jan (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - p. 127-132, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - p. 133-137, 1864 Feb-Sep (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - p. 138-142, 1864 Mar (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - p. 143-149, 1864 Apr 2-19 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - p. 150-154, 1864 Apr 30 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - p. 155-157, 1864 May 1-12 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - p. 158-163, 1864 May 19-31 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - p. 164-166, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - p. 166: Leatherbound notebook, 1857 Aug 11-Nov 5 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - p. 167-172, 1864 Jun-Aug (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - p. 173-176, 1864 Aug-Sep (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - p. 177-178, 1864 Oct 3-8 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - p. 179-180, 182-184, 1864 Oct 12-29 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - p. 185, 187-190, 1864 Nov (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - p. 191-197, 199-201, 1864 Dec (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - p. 202-210, 1865 Jan-Feb (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - p. 211-216, 1865 Mar (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - p. 217-222, 1865 Apr (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - p. 223-232, 1865 May-Jun (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - p. 233-237, 1865 Jul-Aug (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - p. 238-241, 1865 Aug (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - p. 242-246, 1865 Sep (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - VOLUME III, 1865-1869
    - Index (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - p. 1-4, 1865 Sep-Oct (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - p. 5-8, 1865 Nov (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - p. 9-14, 1865 Dec (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - p. 15-20, 1866 Jan (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - p. 21-24, 1866 Feb (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - p. 25-29, 1866 Mar (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - p. 30-35, 1866 Apr (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - p. 36-41, 1866 May (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - p. 42-45, 1866 Jun (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - p. 46-50, 1866 Jul (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - p. 51-56, 1866 Aug (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - p. 57-60, 1866 Aug-Sep (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - p. 61-64, 1866 Nov (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - p. 65-71, 1866 Dec (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - p. 72-78, 1867 Jan (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - p. 79-85, 1867 Feb-Mar (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - p. 86-91, 1867 Apr (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - p. 92-97, 1867 May (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - p. 98-103, 1867 Jun (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - p. 104-110, 1867 Jul (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - p. 111-118, 1867 Aug (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - p. 119-122, 1867 Sep (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - p. 123-128, 1867 Oct (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - p. 129-131, 1867 Nov (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - p. 132-138, 1867 Dec (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - p. 139-147, 1868 Jan-Feb (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - p. 148-155, 1868 Mar-Apr (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - p. 156-162, 1868 Apr-May (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - p. 163-167, 1868 May (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - p. 168-171, 1868 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - p. 172-174, 1868 Jun (Box 3, Folder 109)
      Includes two 1915 letters regarding Lauderdale's loan of photographs to the American Museum of Natural History
      Also store in: Oversize, box 19, folder 567
    - p. 175-180, 1868 Jul (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - p. 181-189, 1868 Aug-Sep (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - p. 190-195, 1868 Sep-Oct (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - p. 196-199, 1868 Sep-Oct (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - p. 200-205, 1868 Nov (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - p. 206-210, 1868 Dec (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - p. 211-220, 1869 Jan-Mar (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - p. 221-225, 1869 Mar (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - p. 226-229, 1869 Apr (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - p. 230-237, 1869 May-Jun (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - p. 238-245, 1869 Jul (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - p. 246-248, 1869 Aug (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - p. 249-252, 1869 Aug-Sep (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - VOLUME IV, 1869-1873
    - Index (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - p. 1-6, 1869 Sep-Oct (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - p. 7-10, 1869 Oct (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - p. 11-14, 1869 Nov (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - p. 15-21, 1869 Dec (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - p. 22-28, 1870 Jan (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - p. 29-33, 1870 Feb (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - p. 34-41, 1870 Mar-Apr (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - p. 42-47, 1870 Apr (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - p. 48-56, 1870 May-Jun (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - p. 57-62, 1870 Jun-Jul (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - p. 63-69, 1870 Jul (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - p. 70-74, 1870 Aug (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - p. 75-77, 1870 Aug-Sep (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - p. 78-82, 1870 Sep (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - p. 83-88, 1870 Oct-Nov (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - p. 89-92, 1870 Nov-Dec (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - p. 93-96, 1870 Dec (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - p. 97-101, 1871 Jan-Feb (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - p. 102-104, 1871 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - p. 105-107, 1871 Mar (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - p. 108-111, 1871 Apr (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - p. 112-119, 1871 May-Jun (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - p. 120-124, 1871 Jul (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - p. 125-130, 1871 Aug-Sep (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - p. 131-134, 1871 Sep (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - p. 135-139, 1871 Oct-Nov (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - p. 140-145, 1871 Nov-Dec (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - p. 146-149, 1871 Dec (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - p. 150-155, 1872 Jan-Feb (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - p. 156-160, 1872 Apr-May (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - p. 161-164, 1872 Jun (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - p. 165-172, 1872 Jul-Aug (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - p. 173-177, 1872 Aug-Sep (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - p. 178-183, 1872 Sep-Oct (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - p. 184-188, 1872 Oct-Nov (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - p. 189-192, 1872 Jan-Nov, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - p. 193-198, 1872 Dec (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - p. 199-203, 1873 Jan-Feb (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - p. 204-207, 1873 Feb (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - p. 208-215, 1873 Mar (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - p. 216-220, 1873 Apr (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - p. 221-225, 1873 May (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - p. 226-233, 1873 Jun (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - p. 234-240, 1873 Jul-Aug (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - p. 241-243, 1873 Aug (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - p. 244-250, 1873 Sep-Oct (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - p. 251-254, 1873 Oct-Nov (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - p. 255-258, 1873 Nov (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - VOLUME V, 1873-1877
    - Index (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - p. 1-6, 1873 Dec (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - p. 7-10, 1874 Jan-Feb (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - p. 11-15, 1874 Feb (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - p. 16-20, 1874 Mar-Apr (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - p. 21-25, 1874 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - p. 26-29, 1874 May (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - p. 30-37, 1874 Jun-Jul (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - p. 38-42, 1874 Jul-Aug (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - p. 43-45, 1874 Aug 9-10 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - p. 46-51, 1874 Aug 11-26 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - p. 52-58, 1874 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - p. 59-62, 1874 Oct (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - p. 63-64, 1874 Oct (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - p. 65-68, 1874 Oct (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - p. 69-70, 1874 Oct (Box 5, Folder 186a)
    - p. 71-76, 1874 Nov (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - p. 77-82, 1874 Nov-Dec (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - p. 83-88, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - p. 89-92, 1875 Feb-Mar (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - p. 93-96, 1875 Mar (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - p. 97-101, 1875 Apr (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - p. 102-105, 1875 May 9-23 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - p. 106-108, 1875 May 15-25 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - p. 109-114, 1875 Jun-Jul (Box 6, Folder 195)
    - p. 115-119, 1875 Jul (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - p. 120-126, 1875 Aug-Sep (Box 6, Folder 197)
    - p. 127-129, 1875 Sep-Oct (Box 6, Folder 198)
    - p. 130, 1875 Sep (Box 6, Folder 199-199a)
    - p. 131-132, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - p. 133-135, 1875 Oct (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - p. 136-140, 1875 Nov (Box 6, Folder 202)
    - p. 141-145, 1875 Dec (Box 6, Folder 203)
    - p. 146-151, 1876 Jan-Feb (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - p. 152-155, 1876 Feb (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - p. 156-160, 1876 Mar-Apr (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - p. 161-165, 1876 Apr (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - p. 166-169, 1876 May-Jun (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - p. 170-172, 1876 Jun (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - p. 173-177, 1876 Jul (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - p. 178-182, 1876 Aug-Sep (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - p. 183-189, 1876 Sep (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - p. 190-195, 1876 Oct-Nov (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - p. 196-199, 1876 Nov-Dec (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - p. 200-206, 1876 Dec (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - p. 207-211, 1877 Jan-Feb (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - p. 212-215, 1877 Feb-Mar (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - p. 216-220, 1877 Mar (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - p. 221-229, 1877 Apr-May (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - p. 230-234, 1877 May-Jun (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - p. 235-238, 1877 Jun (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - p. 239-242, 1877 Jul-Aug (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - p. 243-246, 1877 Aug-Sep (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - p. 247-250, 1877 Sep (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - VOLUME VI, 1877-1881
    - Index (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - p. 1-5, 1877 Oct-Nov (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - p. 6-11, 1877 Nov-Dec (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - p. 12-16, 1877 Dec-1878 Jan (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - p. 17-20, 1878 Jan-Feb (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - p. 21-27, 1878 Feb-Mar (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - p. 28-31, 1878 Mar (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - p. 32-36, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - p. 37-42, 1878 Apr-May (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - p. 43-49, 1878 May-Jun (Box 7, Folder 234)
    - p. 50-59, 1878 Apr, Jun (Box 7, Folder 235)
    - p. 60-67, 1878 Jun-Aug (Box 7, Folder 236)
    - p. 68-71, 1878 Jul-Aug (Box 7, Folder 237)
    - p. 72-75, 1878 Aug (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - p. 76-81, 1878 Sep-Oct (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - p. 82-86, 1878 Oct (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - p. 87-94, 1878 Nov-Dec (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - p. 95-98, 1879 Jan-Mar (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - p. 99-113, 1879 Mar-Apr (Box 7, Folder 243-44)
    - p. 114-117, 1879 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - p. 118-123, 1879 May (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - p. 124-127, 1879 Jun (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - p. 128-132, 1879 Jul-Aug (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - p. 133-136, 1879 Aug (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - p. 137-141, 1879 Sep-Oct (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - p. 142-143, 1879 Oct (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - p. 144-146, 1879 Oct-Nov (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - p. 147-149, 1879 Nov-Dec (Box 7, Folder 253)
    - p. 150-154, 1879 Dec-1880 Jan (Box 7, Folder 254)
    - p. 155-158, 1880 Jan (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - p. 159-167, 1880 Feb (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - p. 168-174, 1880 Mar-Apr (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - p. 175-180, 1880 Apr-May (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - p. 181-185, 1880 May (Box 7, Folder 259)
    - p. 186-189, 1880 Jun-July (Box 7, Folder 260)
    - p. 190-191, 1880 Oct (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - p. 192-201, 1880 Nov-Dec (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - p. 202-204, 1880 Dec (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - p. 205-209, 1881 Jan-Feb (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - p. 210-213, 1881 Feb-Mar (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - p. 214-217, 1881 Mar-Apr (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - p. 218-221, 1881 Apr-May (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - p. 222-226, 1881 May-Jun (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - p. 227-230, 1881 Jun-Jul (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - p. 231-234, 1881 Jul (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - p. 235-240, 1881 Aug-Sep (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - p. 241-243, 1881 Sep (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - VOLUME VII, 1881-1885
    - Index (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - p. 1-5, 1881 Oct-Nov (Box 7, Folder 274)